Once again a very warm welcome to all of you on the YouTube channel,
you are watching
Hindustan Ki Jhalak, friends, in today's
video we will talk about error code 827 and the
second code 814, so let's
start the video quickly, friends, here
you are applying for the Chief Minister's scheme in Jharkhand,
doing KYC and in the
end you make the payment, then you
see the error code 827 and for some people 814
is visible, so what is its solution,
how to solve it, why is this problem occurring,
in today's video we are going to give you complete
information, so let's move the video
forward and tell you why is this error occurring,
why is this problem being seen,
see friends, here
a notification has been issued by CSC for all the CSC people,
you must be seeing it on the screen, see here,
important information for everyone, it is showing many really
CSC IDs in active, all
those who are getting this message, all those people will get
approximately
₹ 250 times the amount of the ESRAM card they have made  If you have made 500 then
you have to multiply ₹250 by 500, that is,
you will deduct ₹1250 from your wallet, only then
your problem will be solved, see, put it
in the wallet, the ID will be activated, then you must have got the
information in this video,
why is this error coming,
what is the problem, I hope
you liked this video and found it helpful,
you can tell us by commenting whether
you liked the video or not and help
Jai Bharat